

Contacts

+48 (576) 528-232 kristina.salnyk@gmail.com @kristina_salnyk

<u>Linkedin</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

Bielsko-Biała, Śląskie, Poland

Tech skills

- HTML / CSS / SASS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- WebPack
- Parsel
- React
- Redux
- React Native
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- SQL
- REST API
- Git

Soft skills

- The maximum contribution to common goals
- Exceptionally willing and successful as a team worker
- Optimal workflow organization
- Competent communication and search for compromises

Languages

- Ukrainian Proficiency
- English Intermediate
- Polish Elementary

Kristina Salnyk

Fullstack Developer

I am a qualified specialist in the field of information technologies aimed at self-realization as a fullstack developer and strive to contribute to the creation of modern and efficient web applications. I possess markup and programming technologies that are current and fully meet the standards of the last 2 years and ready to expand and use them in practice. I am directed to excellent communication and harmonious teamwork. I agree about passing the internship period and studying additional technologies and frameworks

Project Experience

Green Land [.apk file][React Native, JavaScript, Expo, REST API] - Link

The mobile app provides a service for creating and searching for points of waste sorting. Team project, role: Dev. Implementation of the global state using the context, navigation config, creation of screens and logic for user registration, login and logout, profile management, and functionality from the side of the service provider company. Integration with the backend using Axios. Styling with Styled-Components.

Phone Book [React, Redux Toolkit, JavaScript, REST API, Material-UI] - Link

A web application for working with a collection of contacts and the possibility of user authorization. Using asynchronous Redux within Redux Toolkit for state management. Implementation of private and restricted routes for authorized users. Styling components exclusively with the Material-UI library.

Filmoteka [JavaScript, DOM, Handlebars, AJAX, Axios, FireBase, SASS] - <u>Link</u>

A website for searching and saving movies, integrated with The Movie DB. Team project, role: Team Lead. Organization of the team's work, division of tasks, and assistance to project participants. Creation of the structure and configuration of the project using the Parcel bundler. Creation of shared markup and markup of collection elements using Handlebars, and stylization of elements using SASS. Implementation of the user authorization functionality and saving data using the integration with Firebase.

Donut Masterclass [HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, Parcel] - Link

Responsive layout for a website presenting a master class on making donuts. Team project: Dev.

Creating a site heading, and implementing a burger menu by opening a modal window. The stylization of elements by SASS preprocessor, using SCC-animations. Image optimization for different types of devices. Writing simple scripts for page interactivity.

Work Experience

Tring Corp. I Apr 2022 - Oct 2022 (7 months)

QA Automation Engineer

- · Creation of automated test-scenarios, designing and performance of tests, drawing up of bug-reports in Jira
- Writing behavior-driven development test-scenarios in Java using the Cucumber framework, cross-browser testing of web-based applications using Selenium WebDriver
- Building and running tests to support continuous integration using Jenkins Pipeline
- Work with AWS Azure cloud technologies

EFSOL Corp. I Jan 2018 - Mar 2022 (4 years 2 months)

1C Developer

- Automation of the activities of the client company based on 1C: Enterprise (updating, supporting, and administration of typical and non-standard configurations; development of configurations for the customer tasks; analysis, description, and implementation of the company's business processes)
- Implementation of the exchange of the central database with the company's website and mobile application
 using REST and SOAP APIs; integration with online cash registers (ATOL, Mobika, ibox); Google Drive
 integration; integration with SMS services of telecom operators, etc
- Creation of mobile applications for Android OS on 1C: Enterprise mobile platform
- Implementation of interactive maps in JavaScript using the Leaflet library and Yandex API
- Work with SQL queries, configuring MS SQL Server for 1C

Education

Full-stack Development

GolT - Apprenticeship | Mar 2022 - Present

IT Fundamentals, Frontend Course
EPAM Corp. I Mar 2022 - Present

Master's degree, Computer Sciences Sumy State University | Sep 2014 - May 2020 O Software Quality Assurance (QA)
Test Automation (TA)
Netcracker Technology Corp. | Oct 2017

Databases and Information Systems
Netcracker Technology Corp. | Jun 2017

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).